ecopywriters.com 2018-02-28

# Privacy Policy - eCopywriters

Our privacy commitments are fundamental to our business practices. These stringent guidelines are applied to all our business relationships, including clients, members, and website visitors. Through encryption and other security safeguards to protect customer data, we keep all personal information safe.

We will do not sell personal information to anyone, for any purpose. Period.

We fully disclose our privacy policy in plain language, and make this policy easily accessible to you.

We notify clients and members of revisions to our privacy policy, in advance. No surprises. The customers’ choices determine how we use their information for marketing purposes. Customers are in control.

We keep personal information in our business records while you are a member or client, or until it is no longer needed for business, tax or, legal purposes.

We keep personal information safe using encryption or other appropriate security controls. Our privacy policy applies to all uses of our services. We will always provide notice of material changes to this Policy. In order for us to constantly improve our services and relationships, we may collect different types of information that help us learn more about how client and members use our services.

  * ##### Your Personal Information

    * eCopywriters.com owns and manages all of the information collected on this site. We will not sell or rent this information, nor will we share it in ways that differ from what is disclosed in this statement without your consent. Customer information is considered to be an asset of ecopywriters.com and all subsidiary websites, and as such, may be transferred to another company as part of an acquisition of ecopywriters.com

    * eCopywriters.com provides a copywriting service. If you want to learn more about the products we offer, please go to www.ecopywriters.com for more information. If you make a purchase with any eCopywriters.com website, we will include you in our list to receive email updates about special offers, new products and services, and any information we believe will be relevant for our customers. We will never share the information you give us with any other company.

  * ##### IP Addresses & Cookies

    * eCopywriters.com is firmly committed to your privacy. We use your IP address simply to help diagnose problems you may be experiencing on our website. Your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart and to gather broad demographic information. We use this information for purposes such as improving our site based on customer preferences. If you set your browser to reject cookies, some of the features on this site may not work properly. Cookies are never used to store sensitive customer information such as names, addresses, passwords or credit card numbers.

  * ##### External Links

    * This site may contain links to other websites. eCopywriters.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these websites.

  * ##### Address Information

    * Our site uses an order form for you to request information, products and services. We collect your contact information including, but not limited to, street addresses, email addresses, phone numbers, and financial information. Where required, we also share this information with certain intermediaries strictly to process your order. Collected information is securely used to send information to you about your orders, about our company, for billing and/or to contact you when necessary.

  * ##### Security

    * Our website, eCopywriters.com, has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information that we collect. We utilize a firewall and use SSL encryption to keep this information secure.

  * ##### Privacy Policy Changes

    * If we decide to change our privacy policy in whole or in part, we will inform you by posting a notice on our website.Those changes will go into effect on the date posted in the notice and will apply to all users of www.eCopywriters.com. The effective date of this revised Privacy Policy is as of March 10, 2009.

Thank you for visiting with us.

E-mail:[info@eCopywriters.com](mailto:ecopywriters@gmail.com)
